export const data =[
 
    {
        question:"Which is the biggest continent in the earth",
        option1:"Africa",
        option2:"Europe",
        option3:"North America",
        option4:"Asia",
        ans: 4,
    }
 ,

 {
    question:"Who is current president of America",
    option1:"Donal Trump",
    option2:"Joe Biden",
    option3:"Obema",
    option4:"Jarge Push",
    ans:2 ,
}
,
{
    question:"Which country has most countries",
    option1:"North America",
    option2:"Africa",
    option3:"Asia",
    option4:"Europe",
    ans: 2,
}
,
{
    question:"When India gets Freedom Britan",
    option1:"1970",
    option2:"1947",
    option3:"1949",
    option4:"1943",
    ans: 2,
}
,
{
    question:"What is the national bird of USA",
    option1:"Eagle",
    option2:"Peacock",
    option3:"Parrot",
    option4:"Owl",
    ans: 1,
}
,
{
    question:"Indai has hwo many states",
    option1:"20",
    option2:"29",
    option3:"30",
    option4:"28",
    ans: 4,
}
,
{
    question:"What is the rank of India in Gdp ",
    option1:"5",
    option2:"10",
    option3:"2",
    option4:"4",
    ans:1 ,
}
,
{
    question:"What is National Sport of India",
    option1:"Foot Ball",
    option2:"Hockey",
    option3:"Voley Ball",
    option4:"Cricket",
    ans: 2,
}
,
    {
    question:"What is the biggest desert in the World",
    option1:"Nambiea",
    option2:"Sahara",
    option3:"Kalahari",
    option4:"Savana",
    ans: 2,
}
,
{
    question:"How many Oceans  are in Earth",
    option1:"7",
    option2:"4",
    option3:"8",
    option4:"4",
    ans:1,
}
,
{
    question:"What is National Bird of India",
    option1:"Peacock",
    option2:"Crow",
    option3:"Eagle",
    option4:"Parrot",
    ans:4 ,
}
,
{
    question:"What is the Biggest river in the world",
    option1:"Nile",
    option2:"Amazon",
    option3:"Kalahari",
    option4:"Savana",
    ans:1 ,
}
,
{
    question:"When America launched Atomicbomb on Japan",
    option1:"1947",
    option2:"1956",
    option3:"1946",
    option4:"1945",
    ans: 4,
}
,
{
    question:"When World-war I was happened",
    option1:'1941-1945',
    option2:'1912-1920',
    option3:'1911-1915',
    option4:'1920-1923',
    ans:3
}
,
{
    question:"What is the extension of RAM",
    option1:"Reduce Access Memory",
    option2:"Random Access Memory ",
    option3:"Reduce Accessable Memory ",
    option4:"Rondom Adjustable Memory ",
    ans:2
},
{
    question:"Which is the framework for the Javascript from the belows ",
    option1:"ES6 ",
    option2:"Applet ",
    option3:"Javax ",
    option4:"Angular ",
    ans: 4
}
,
{
    question:"Wich is the extension of ROM ",
    option1:"Reduce Complete Memory ",
    option2:"Random original memory ",
    option3:"Read Only Memory ",
    option4:"Read and Access Memory ",
    ans:3
}
,
{
    question:"What rendering will do in React ",
    option1:"Gathering data before it pass to to Browser DOM  ",
    option2:"Display data after it  pass to the Browser DOM ",
    option3:"Gatering the required data ",
    option4:"Displaying the required data ",
    ans:1
}
,
{
    question:"In below , what is non Javascript Framework ",
    option1:"Angular ",
    option2:"Jquery ",
    option3:"Bootstrap ",
    option4:"Applet ",
    ans:4
}
,
{
    question:"What is the extension of API ",
    option1:"Adjustable Programming Interface ",
    option2:"Application progrmming Interface ",
    option3:"Application Project Interface ",
    option4:"Adjustable Project Interface ",
    ans:2
},
{
    question:"What keyword is used to get the component in React ",
    option1:"Interface ",
    option2:"Class ",
    option3:"Render ",
    option4:"function ",
    ans:3
},
{
    question:"Which symbol is used instead of function keyword ",
    option1:"=> ",
    option2:"==> ",
    option3:"* ",
    option4:"|| ",
    ans:1
},
{
    question:"Which symbol is used in Terniory Operator ",
    option1:"* ",
    option2:"#",
    option3:"& ",
    option4:"? ",
    ans:4
},
{
    question:"What cocept is used with function compoent in React ",
    option1:"Class ",
    option2:"Hooks ",
    option3:"Interface ",
    option4:"Arrow fuction ",
    ans:2
},
{
    question:"Where we should declare hooks in the program ",
    option1:"Top of the program page ",
    option2:"When we are using Hooks ",
    option3:"Top of the function component ",
    option4:"After using the Hooks ",
    ans:3
},
];